{
    "id": "ab4ef09746f5451d80b288e392e92078",
    "title": "Conjunctions And Transitional Adverbs Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "................................. it was raining, we went for a walk.",
            "description": "Though is a conjunction used to connect two contrasting ideas.",
            "answers": [
                "Though",
                "Despite",
                "However"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "41b912c811b941299f1a44a858ddf736"
        },
        {
            "question": "It was cold ............................... we enjoyed the evening.",
            "description": "However is a transitional adverb it does not connect the two clauses. ",
            "answers": [
                "however",
                "though",
                "despite"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "a0d0c61785b441d8940b819e2500cbb6"
        },
        {
            "question": "................................ burning the midnight oil, we could not meet the deadline.",
            "description": "Despite is a conjunction it is followed by a preposition or an ing form.",
            "answers": [
                "Despite",
                "However",
                "Though"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "68df1ed8bee2405ab2e86870365eb94a"
        },
        {
            "question": "He is the most experienced guy in the team .................................. he isn't the best.",
            "description": "But is used to connect two contrasting ideas.",
            "answers": [
                "but",
                "however",
                "despite"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "fd30950ea060467eb3ffbb027b5f9464"
        },
        {
            "question": "................................. she earns well, she never seems to have enough money.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "Though",
                "However",
                "Despite"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "ade13f3ab09b48eb88dc04f80d953fa6"
        },
        {
            "question": "............................... their best efforts, they could not save her.",
            "description": "Despite is a preposition. It is followed by a noun or ing form.",
            "answers": [
                "Despite",
                "Though",
                "However"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "288d2e9697f8494faccfecc721814cb5"
        },
        {
            "question": "He was the most deserving candidate ..............................., he did not get the promotion.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "however",
                "though",
                "despite"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "16f87dbc80ae4d0798bb3f5f1f64be33"
        },
        {
            "question": ".................................... she has many health problems, she attends office regularly.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "Although",
                "However",
                "Despite"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "f03a70931e9d4b819e58f8827406f24d"
        },
        {
            "question": "She succeeded in life .................................. facing several setbacks.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "despite",
                "however",
                "in spite of"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "25d6aa40e65f41e7a1cb3a66911b318c"
        },
        {
            "question": "................................... she had a bad teacher, she passed the test.",
            "description": "Though is a conjunction used to connect two clauses expressing contrasting ideas.",
            "answers": [
                "Though",
                "However",
                "Despite"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "9840077ff1f44b09840227da483e3f09"
        },
        {
            "question": "She is not very humble ..............................., I can't help loving her.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "though",
                "however",
                "despite"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "9d04533062d841d199357d2ef370e66c"
        },
        {
            "question": "..................................... he is intelligent, he is very lazy.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "Though",
                "However",
                "Despite"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "53dbf7cb53404328af1fc0541ee79b6e"
        }
    ]
}